<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Savease</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home">Home</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="nav_header_title">Android Studio</string>
    <string name="nav_header_subtitle">android.studio@android.com</string>
    <string name="nav_header_desc">Navigation header</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <string name="next"></string>
    <string name="skip">SKIP</string>
    <string name="start">GOT IT</string>

    <string name="slide_1_title">Quality Tutor!</string>
    <string name="slide_1_desc">We assure you and your child quality tutors equipped to fit the need of your child!</string>

    <string name="slide_2_title">Guaranteed Academic Success</string>
    <string name="slide_2_desc">Equipped with the best tutor and an awesome child, we confidently guarantee sure academic success!</string>

    <string name="slide_3_title">Real time progress</string>
    <string name="slide_3_desc">Monitor and track the progress of your child at your own comfort!</string>

    <string name="slide_4_title">World Travel</string>
    <string name="slide_4_desc">Book tickets of any transportation and travel the world!</string>

    <string name="play_again_desc">To see the welcome slider again, goto Settings -> apps -> Primedclass -> clear data</string>
    <string name="play_again">Play Again</string>


    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder user -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="to_make_a_deposit_transaction_kindly_click_on_the_dropdown_tab_or_button_to_select_the_appropriate_account_type_you_could_select_a_savease_account_or_other_banks_if_your_recipient_account_is_not_a_savease_account_type_if_your_recipient_exist_under_the_other_bank_option_kindly_select_the_appropriate_bank_as_available_in_the_dropdown_tab_insert_the_account_number_of_the_recipient_and_click_the_verify_button_to_verify_the_account_number_provided_the_account_name_associated_with_the_accountwill_automatically_be_generated_if_correct_proceed_to_insert_the_purchased_voucher_and_type_in_the_narration_for_your_deposit_proceed_to_make_deposit_then_select_as_shown_on_the_screen_a_transaction_alert_is_generated_and_account_credited_as_appropriate_you_could_also_select_saved_beneficiary_option_if_you_had_saved_a_beneficiary_for_a_quick_deposit_process">To make a deposit transaction, Kindly click on the dropdown tab or button to select the appropriate account type. You could select a savease account or other banks if your recipient account is not a savease account type. If your recipient exist under the other bank option. Kindly select the appropriate bank as available in the dropdown tab. Insert the account number of the recipient and click the verify button to verify the account number provided. The account name associated with the accountwill automatically be generated if correct, proceed to insert the purchased voucher, and type in the narration for your deposit. Proceed to Make deposit, then select as shown on the screen. A transaction alert is generated and account credited as appropriate. You could also select saved Beneficiary option, if you had saved a beneficiary for a quick deposit process.</string>
    <string name="title_activity_home_regular_user">HomeRegularUser</string>
    <string name="to_do_a_transfer_transaction_click_on_the_dropdown_tab_or_button_to_select_the_appropriate_account_type_you_could_select_a_saveaseaccount_or_other_bank_if_the_recipient_account_is_not_a_savease_account_type_if_your_recipient_exist_under_the_other_bank_option_select_the_appropriate_bank_as_available_in_the_drop_down_tab">To do a Transfer Transaction, Click on the dropdown tab or button to select the appropriate account type. You could select a saveaseaccount or other bank if the recipient account is not a savease account type, If your recipient exist under the other bank option. Select the appropriate bank as available in the drop down tab.</string>
    <string name="about_savease">
        Africa\'s Easy Deposit &amp; Payment Gateway\n\n Savease was established to create simple solutions to complex savings and payment problem. It was designed and created to initiate, develop and modernise payment system.\n\n In 2012, the Central Bank of Nigeria created a Vision 2020 Cashless Policy the for a number of key reasons, including: \n\n 1. To drive development and modernization of our payment system in line with Nigeria\'s vision 2020 goal of being amongst the top 20 economies by the end of 2020. An efficient and modern payment system is positively correlated with economic development and is a key enabler for economic growth.\n\n 2. To reduce the cost of Banking services (including cost of credit) and drive financial inclusion by providing more efficient transaction options and greater reach.\n\n 3. To improve the effectiveness of Monetary Policy in managing inflation and driving economic growth.\n\n In addition, the CBN Vision 2020 Cashless Policy aims to curb some of the negative consequences associated with the high usage of physical cash in the economy including:\n\n 1. High Cost of Cash\n 2. High Risk of Using Cash\n 3. Informal Economy\n 4. High Subsidy\n Inefficiency &amp; Corruption\n\n In line with the policy by the CBN, we have designed and created a product called SAVEASE, to:\n\n 1. Bank the Unbanked\n 2. Fund the Unfunded Accounts\n 3. Implement the Cashless Policy of the CBN\n 4. Curb the Spread of the Deadly Corona Virus\n 5. Reduce Unemployment in Nigeria\n\nAs indicated in our Memorandum of Association with the Corporate Affair Commission, the Objects for which the Company was established are:\n\n 1. To develop and design micro softwares, internet/website designing to ease the banking system and sales of goods.\n 2. To carry on business with Banks in Nigeria in implementing the Cashless Policy of the Central Bank of Nigeria.\n 3. To intimate the average Nigerian on Banking Policies and the effect of Banking. To carry on business of general contracts, imports, exports of general goods, general merchants, to act as a manufacturer representative for this purpose. \n 4. To develop products that will benefit Nigerians and the Nigerian Banks.\n\nWe recognise the banking constraint of distance, time, space and structure which is experienced when making small scale deposit payments into banks; thus, we created an excellent solution to this experience.\n\n We recognise the large number of unbanked population in the country; thus, we created a perfect product to enable grassroots banking.\n\n We recognise the large number of unfunded bank accounts which in turn affects the potential financial base of financial institutions like yours; thus, we have created a service which allows making deposits from the comfort of anywhere.\n\n We recognise the need to drive development and modernisation of our payment system in line with CBN’s Vision 2020 which is indicated in the Cashless Policy of the CBN; thus we created a modernised simple payment gateway which allows Users to pay for goods and service (transactions) without the use of physical cash.\n\n We recognise that unemployment is on the rise, as many Nigerians are without jobs or a means of livelihood; thus, we are creating job opportunities and a means of livelihood which will in turn enhance economic development.\n\n We also recognise that a good saving habit is vital to capital development and financial independence; thus we have provided a simple yet compelling tool/approach to help every person achieve this fundamental goal.\n\n We recognise that the easiest way to spread the deadly corona virus is through the medium of exchange called Money; thus we have created an alternative means for making transactions in other to curb the spread of the deadly COVID 19.\n\n It is said that the underlying foundation to good products are made up of 3 components:\n\n * Functionality\n * Reliability\n * Ease of Use\n\n These components are met; thus, qualifying SAVEASE as a good product for the Market. It has been designed to create habits, educate financial literacy, inspire emotions, and ultimately become an indispensable utility tool.
</string>
    <string name="title_activity_fund_account">FundAccount</string>
    <string name="thank_you_for_download_the_savease_app_now_that_you_are_about_registering_to_the_savease_network_please_ensure_to_use_appropriate_information_as_it_appears_on_your_bvn_bank_verification_number_we_mean_firstname_lastname_and_telephone_number_must_be_exactly_as_available_on_your_bvn_this_is_an_important_criteria_to_successfully_activating_your_savease_you_will_not_be_able_to_perform_certain_transaction_if_your_account_is_not_verified_and_linked_to_a_bvn"> \n \nNow that you are about registering to the Savease Network,<u> please ensure to use the appropriate information as it appears on your BVN (Bank Verification Number).</u> <b>We mean: Firstname, Lastname and Telephone number must be exactly as available on your BVN.</b> \n\nThis is an important criteria to successfully activating your Savease.<u> You will not be able to perform certain transactions if your account is not verified and linked to a BVN.</u></string>
    <string name="trust_savease_nto_reach_your_goals"><font color='#FA9928'>Trust </font>Savease\n  to reach your goals</string>
    <string name="teaching_you_about_money"><font color='#212435'>Teaching</font> \nyou about money</string>
    <string name="gaining_financial_freedom"><font color='#FA9928'>Gaining</font> \nfinancial freedom</string>
    <string name="passionate_about_helping_you"><font color='#212435'>Passionate</font> \nabout helping you</string>
    <string name="creating_a_life_time_of_happiness"><font color='#FA9928'>Giving</font> you a life time \nof happiness</string>
    <string name="savease_was_established_to_create_simple_solutions_to_complex_deposit_and_savings_problem_it_is_a_useful_solution_that_will_promote_effective_savings_habit_we_have_created_a_technology_which_uses_instant_deposit_prepaid_scratch_cards_pins_offering_its_users_a_simple_and_convenient_way_to_make_deposits_into_distinctive_bank_accounts_across_the_continent_starting_from_nigeria_with_this_technological_breakthrough_you_can_make_deposit_payments_from_the_comfort_of_anywhere_to_verify_the_validity_of_a_voucher_simply_click_on_the_verify_icon_on_the_dashboard_insert_the_prepaid_pin_then_click_on_the_verify_button_a_pop_up_will_display_on_your_screen_with_information_about_the_card_to_make_a_transfer_transaction_click_on_the_transfer_icon_on_the_dashboard_select_the_appropriate_account_or_wallet_type_from_the_dropdown_menu_you_could_select_savease_wallet_account_if_you_intend_to_make_a_transfer_into_a_savease_account_or_select_bank_account_if_you_intend_to_make_a_deposit_to_a_bank_account_other_than_savease_insert_the_account_number_the_amount_to_be_transferred_a_narration_for_the_transaction_your_secret_pin_then_proceed_to_click_on_the_continue_button_select_confirm_in_the_attestation_box_on_the_screen_or_select_discard_to_discontinue_the_transaction_the_account_so_provided_will_be_automatically_credited_with_the_amount_so_transfer_to_make_a_deposit_transaction_click_on_the_deposit_icon_on_the_dashboard_select_the_appropriate_account_or_wallet_type_from_the_dropdown_menu_you_could_select_my_wallet_account_if_you_intend_to_make_a_deposit_into_your_account_or_select_other_wallet_account_if_you_intend_to_make_a_deposit_to_a_different_recipient_insert_the_account_number_voucher_pin_followed_with_a_narration_for_the_transaction_then_proceed_to_click_the_continue_button_the_account_so_provided_will_be_automatically_credited_with_the_value_of_the_pin_provided_to_do_a_buy_voucher_transaction_make_sure_you_have_adequate_funds_in_your_account_else_fund_your_account_by_clicking_on_the_fund_account_icon_then_follow_through_the_process_using_your_atm_card_before_initiating_this_process_if_account_is_adequately_funded_for_a_potential_transaction_kindly_choose_the_card_denomination_from_the_dropdown_tab_insert_the_quantity_of_voucher_to_be_purchased_into_the_quantity_box_followed_by_your_secret_pin_code_proceed_to_clicking_the_buy_card_button_click_on_terms_and_conditions_if_you_have_not_read_it_before_or_proceed_to_check_the_check_box_to_agree_and_accept_the_terms_and_conditions_proceed_to_place_order_to_complete_your_purchase_or_the_discard_button_to_discard_the_purchase_if_transaction_is_successful_a_successful_alert_will_be_displayed_else_a_not_successful_message_will_be_prompted_thereafter_check_your_voucher_table_from_your_dashboard_and_filter_the_drop_down_tab_to_display_used_cards_the_voucher_table_is_an_environment_which_helps_you_with_the_arrangement_and_management_of_voucher_in_this_section_you_are_presented_with_used_and_unused_cards_to_view_this_select_the_voucher_table_icon_on_your_dashboard_either_select_from_the_dropdown_tab_to_display_your_entire_used_voucher_or_all_unused_vouchers_the_used_voucher_presents_all_details_about_a_used_voucher_it_supplies_you_information_ranging_from_time_date_of_use_name_of_the_user_among_other_details_to_fund_an_account_select_the_fund_account_icon_on_your_dashboard_proceed_to_provide_your_atm_card_details_as_requested_on_the_screen_a_onetime_password_otp_will_be_sent_to_the_telephone_number_of_the_atm_card_to_confirm_ownership_of_the_card_provide_this_otp_and_your_savease_account_will_be_funded_with_the_amount_so_funded_to_view_your_transaction_summary_simply_select_the_statement_icon_on_your_dashboard_you_will_be_presented_with_a_log_of_all_your_transactions_the_account_officer_icon_on_your_dashboard_directs_you_to_the_assigned_savease_personnel_whose_duty_is_to_help_you_understand_money_help_you_with_your_savings_and_ultimately_help_you_gain_financial_freedom_he_she_also_helps_you_in_resolving_any_technical_complaints_that_may_be_observed_feel_free_to_contact_him_her_through_the_channels_so_provided_notifications_are_sent_to_your_notification_box_icon_on_the_dashboard_below_please_ensure_to_always_read_all_messages_that_appear_in_this_box_as_products_and_offers_will_be_sent_to_your_box_transaction_alert_are_stored_in_the_message_icon_that_appears_on_the_top_right_view_of_the_dashboard_here_you_can_confirm_or_refer_transaction_when_necessary_please_ensure_to_send_feedback_through_complaint_icon_seen_below_the_dashboard_thank_you_for_trusting_us_to_help_you">SAVEASE was established to create simple solutions to complex deposit and savings problem. It is a useful solution that will promote effective savings habit. \n\nWe have created a technology which uses instant deposit prepaid scratch cards pins. Offering its users: a simple and convenient way to make deposits into distinctive bank accounts across the continent starting from Nigeria. \n\nWith this technological breakthrough, you can make deposit transaction from anywhere with ease. \n\nTo verify the validity of a voucher, simply click on the Verify icon on the dashboard. Insert the prepaid pin, then click on the verify button. A pop up will display on your screen, with information about the card. \n\nTo make a transfer transaction, click on the Transfer icon on the dashboard, select the appropriate account or wallet type from the dropdown menu. You could select Savease Wallet/Account; if you intend to make a transfer into a Savease account or select Bank Account if you intend to make a deposit to a bank account other than Savease. Insert the account number, the amount to be transferred, a narration for the transaction, your secret pin. Then proceed to click on the continue button. Select confirm in the attestation box on the screen, or select discard to discontinue the transaction. The account so provided will be automatically credited with the amount so transfer. \n\nTo make a deposit transaction, click on the Deposit icon on the dashboard, select the appropriate account or wallet type from the dropdown menu. You could select My Wallet/Account; if you intend to make a deposit into your account or select Other Wallet/Account if you intend to make a deposit to a different recipient. Insert the account number, voucher pin, followed with a narration for the transaction. Then proceed to click the continue button. The account so provided will be automatically credited with the value of the pin provided. \n\nTo do a Buy Voucher transaction make sure you have adequate funds in your account, else fund your account by clicking on the fund account icon; then follow through the process using your ATM card before initiating this process. \n\nIf account is adequately funded for a potential transaction. Kindly choose the card denomination from the dropdown tab. Insert the quantity of voucher to be purchased into the quantity box, followed by your secret pin code. Proceed to clicking the buy card button. Click on terms and conditions if you have not read it before, or proceed to check the check box to agree and accept the terms and conditions. Proceed to Place Order to complete your purchase, or the Discard button to discard the purchase. If transaction is successful, a successful alert will be displayed, else a not successful message will be prompted. Thereafter, check your voucher table from your dashboard, and filter the drop down tab to display used cards. \n\nThe Voucher Table is an environment which helps you with the arrangement and management of voucher. In this section, you are presented with Used and Unused cards. To view this, select the Voucher Table icon on your dashboard. Either select from the dropdown tab to display your entire Used Voucher or all Unused Vouchers. The used voucher presents all details about a used voucher; it supplies you information ranging from time/date of use, name of the user, among other details. \n\nTo fund an account, select the fund account icon on your dashboard. Proceed to provide your ATM card details as requested on the screen. A onetime password (OTP) will be sent to the telephone number of the ATM card to confirm ownership of the card. Provide this OTP, and your Savease Account will be funded with the amount so funded. \n\nTo view your transaction summary, simply select the Statement icon on your dashboard. You will be presented with a log of all your transactions. \n\nThe account officer icon on your dashboard, directs you to the assigned savease personnel, whose duty is to help you understand money, help you with your savings and ultimately help you gain financial freedom. He/she also helps you in resolving any technical complaints that may be observed. Feel free to contact him/her through the channels so provided. \n\nNotifications are sent to your notification box icon on the dashboard below. Please ensure to always read all messages that appear in this box; as products and offers will be sent to your box. \n\nTransaction alert are stored in the message icon that appears on the top right view of the dashboard. Here you can confirm or refer transaction when necessary. \n\nTo make a withdrawal from your account. Click on the withdraw icon, provide the receiving bank account details. Proceed to verify, immediately the system automates your transaction and you will get a credit alert. Please note that you must have a minimum balance of one thousand five hundred naira. \n\nPlease ensure to send feedback through the complaint icon seen below on the dashboard. \n\nThank you for trusting us to help you.\n\n\n\n</string>
    <string name="title_activity_withdraw">WithdrawActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vendor_home">VendorHome</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vendor_settings">VendorSettings</string>
    <string name="title_activity_vendors_around">Map</string>
</resources>
